{
    "id": "9cdb8eb714cd4ff6931b0edcc60b04fd",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You must ................................ follow my instructions or resign.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3b6af7a51c0a4a86a406aee31655a3e2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither John ......................................... Sam could have done this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "nor"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d6469f58e48240e792a42e2f49bf94f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The burglars ............................................ looted the shop but also set fire to it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not only",
                "not just",
                "only"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "26c81da8c9ae4eee805390c8781625a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................. he is hurt he wants to play.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As though",
                "Even if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c5af146ac78248419e93911bec6fca6d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ............................................... weak that he could barely stand.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c6291b25dd994a9cacb706d94c990f0b"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................ you give me the keys of the safe, you will be shot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Without"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "49fa1df55ceb4eb399d2b45b11fd9e22"
        },
        {
            "question": "He would ................................................ eat nor allow us to eat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "neither",
                "either",
                "nor"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "279cb8d9d06c49029bdb8644e16911e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The situation is not ......................................... difficult as people think.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d6bf2b4aee2d4835918e06537980159d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The officer was ........................................ inefficient that he had to be sacked.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "42dc674f507d428385444faaaf1292c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The task is ....................................... difficult that you canâ€™t do it alone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "17b5f6a4cd104117a5909c701f3f0555"
        }
    ]
}